<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Researches on ///dzautner</title>
    <link>https://dzautner.com/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Researches on ///dzautner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dzautner.com/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Trauma Dissociation and Life Focus: A Structural Dissociation Theory Perspective</title>
      <link>https://dzautner.com/research/trauma/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dzautner.com/research/trauma/</guid>
      <description>Trauma Dissociation and Life Focus: A Structural Dissociation Theory Perspective Daniel Zautner&#xA;Independent Researcher&#xA;March 5, 2024&#xA;Abstract The present study investigates the relationships between trauma, dissociation, life focus, stress resilience, and demographic factors in a sample of Finnish residents (N = 100) through the lens of structural dissociation theory. Structural dissociation theory posits that trauma can lead to a division of the personality into an apparently normal part (ANP) and an emotional part (EP).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Distributed Computation Marketplace over Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://dzautner.com/research/distributed-computing-over-blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dzautner.com/research/distributed-computing-over-blockchain/</guid>
      <description>We describe a Blockchain based1, peer-to-peer network of distributed computers solving arbitrary, strictly-defined problems for a financial incentive in the form of a cryptographic currency2.&#xA;The computational problems are signed and posted to the blockchain in a contract describing the minimal computational unit (MCU) of the problem, the price per MCU, a method for joining the results of different Solvers, and a test for the validity of a solution.&#xA;The Solver will transmit the solutions to the Bidder off the blockchain to avoid any space-complexity issues and eliminate the potential for network flooding with bogus or trivial solutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On eBay&#39;s Imperial Roman Coin market and History</title>
      <link>https://dzautner.com/research/coins/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 15:37:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dzautner.com/research/coins/</guid>
      <description>eBay&amp;rsquo;s Ancient Roman Coin market is likely the largest market place for ancient coins in today&amp;rsquo;s world. Hundreds of thousands of ancient items exchanged hands through eBay&amp;rsquo;s marketplace in the last year.&#xA;In the last 7 months, more than a quarter of a million coins been listed on eBay alone.&#xA;Given the inherit historical value in ancient coins and my personal interest in them, I have been collecting data on every Roman Imperial Coin listing on eBay for the past seven months.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Most Documented War in History: Who talks about it?</title>
      <link>https://dzautner.com/research/syria2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 15:37:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dzautner.com/research/syria2/</guid>
      <description>The discussion about the ongoing war in the context of geo-politics, modern warfare, and even morality is one that is as important as it is active. The more we discuss the war, the more we learn from it, and the less likely we are to repeat it.&#xA;But the discussion of war itself is reflecting those same issues it attempts to make sense of.&#xA;The human tendency for discussing the atrocities of war, and the ease of which one can, with malice or without, lead discussions and persuade the impressionable is not left unnoticed by the leading actors and the partisans the war gave birth to.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Most Documented War in History: The TOW Program</title>
      <link>https://dzautner.com/research/syria/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2016 15:37:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dzautner.com/research/syria/</guid>
      <description>In mid 2012, The former head of Syria&amp;rsquo;s chemical weapons, Major General Adnan Silu, declared that “All we need from NATO are two air attacks on the presidential palace to topple the regime and we will be able to control all the Syrian cities”.&#xA;But two years later, amid clashes between the rebel fractions and the now independent ISIS (a few months before they would declare their Caliphate) the rebels and their supporters were not as optimistic.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
